<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<root xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<item ID="101">
		<talk>#0| (There’s a rabbit beside a guillotine.)
#1| I don't feel like living anymore.
#1| Life has no meaning for me anymore. I'm gonna do it purrr.
#0| What happened man?
#0| Tell me about it, maybe I can help.
#1| You would not understand purrr!
#1| My entire life has been a lie purrr!
#1| You can not imagine how it feels when what you belief were overthrown-ed purrr.
#0| Oh man, I'm really sorry.
#0| I'm just a ghost, you know. I could only imagine your pain.
#1| You just don't get it do you?
#1| I use to believe that carrot is the best thing on earth, and yet it tasted like sh*t purrr!
#0| Wait, what?
#1| It's disgusting! And too sweet! It's like an orange potato soaked in sugary water purrr!
#1| Ah man you made me think about it again! I just have to die now purrr!
#0| (Oh god I have to help this thing.) 
</talk>

	</item>
	
	<item ID="102">
		<talk>#1| Stop bothering me purrr！
#0| hey, just calm down...
#1| Can't you just leave me alone purr?
#2|Sure-1001+No-1002</talk>

	</item>
	
	<item ID="103">
		<talk>#0| Looks like the tortoise strikes again.
#1|	Let me go！
#0| You have to promise me that you won't suicide for a carrot again.
#1| What if I don't?
#0| (stare)
#1| ...
#0| (firmly stare)
#1| ...
#0| (staring like you will never see things again)
#1| ...
#1| Fine——I wont try it again.
#0| You promise?
#1| I promise——
#0| Good...rabbit.
#1| ...You just won't understand.
#0| ...
#1| I'm leaving now.
#0| Be careful. See you.
#1| ...Bye</talk>

	</item>
	
	<item ID="201">
		<talk>#0| (Back to the old place again, that rabbit isn't here right?)
#0| Oh god, why are still here?
#1| No...You must mistake me as someone else. Pu...hhh.
#1| I am... Sir Handsome Mustache, not...
#2| Alright, I guess I do mistake you. -2001+Errr...I think not.-2002</talk>

	</item>
	
	<item ID="202">
		<talk>#0| Why are there so many traps and buttons here?
#1| Hey, don't ask me. I'm just been resourceful here.
#0| Why do you only go in a straight line then?
#1| It's just the way I walk. And...
#0| And?
#1| And I don't like pain...
#0| I don't like it either.
#1| I really don't like it.
#1| So I just wanna it to be over soon.
#1| That's why I closed my eyes and just ram into it.
#1| Beside, you are a ghost, Can you even feel pain?
#0| I can't, ghosts don't have hearts, so they can't feel pain.
#0| But I'm not always a ghost, so I do understand what is pain.
#1| I'm starting to get jealous of you now.
#1| You know what, ghost rabbit sounds pretty cool, Here I come!</talk>
	</item>
	
	<item ID="203">
		<talk>#1| Are you stopping me because ghost rabbit is much cooler than you?
#0| Ghost rabbit is not cooler...
#0| Alright, to be fair, ghost rabbit would be pretty cool.
#0| But you can't become a ghost, and ghosts are not cool.
#1| Yes they are.
#0| No they are not.
#1| How does someone become a ghost then?
#0| I'm not gonna tell you, you know.
#1| Well, guess I will just die then.
#0| No, you made your promise yesterday.
#1| I promised to not die for a carrot, I have a lot of other trouble beside carrots.
#1| And no one wants me to live anyway.
#0| Hey, how about me? 
#1| ...
#0| Listen, I've gotta go now. Ghosts can't hang around for too long.
#0| But you have to promise me that you live at least till tomorrow.
#0| I'll come back here for you tomorrow, you just calm down until we meet again.
#1| ...Fine, just this time purrr. For the fact that you said ghost rabbit is cool.
#0| See you tomorrow!
#1| ...see you purrr.</talk>
	</item>
	
	<item ID="301">
		<talk>#0| (Of course it’s here.)
#1| A wild rabbit appeared!
#2|Run-3001+Talk-3002</talk>
	</item>
	
	<item ID="302">
		<talk>#1| Uh, what is this?
#1| Hmmm, the wind is too strong, I'm going to be blown away, purrr!
#0| Hold on, I'm coming!</talk>
	</item>
	
	<item ID="303">
		<talk>#0| Got you!
#1| Purrr! !
#1| Well, man, I thought I was about to...
#0| die?
#1| Well... Yes...
#1| It’s not like I’m afraid of it purrr! I just want to leave peacefully.
#1| Instead of being blown away by an electric fan or something.
#1| ...
#0| I understand that you do have difficulties.
#0| But I hope you can make the decision after you really think about it.
#0| It's time you told me why.
#1| I... Okay...
#1| I’ll tell you now...</talk>
	</item>
	
	<item ID="401">
		<talk>#1| As you can see, I am just an ordinary rabbit.
#1| I have no specialties and no friends.
#1| I have no dreams either.
#1| Others around me tell me what's interesting and what's meaningful.
#1| I just followed.
#1| And by now, I have nothing left to do.
#1| I no have goals or purposes to live purrr.
#0|(No, not like this)
#0|(Life should not be like this. )
#0| Listen, I ...(rumbling)
#0| I ...(rumbling)
#0| I ...(rumbling)
#0| ...... (......)
#0| I ...(rumbling)
#0| What's going on here? (There are more new traps around. )
#0| Can't you wait for me to finish? (Nah. )
#0| (You have to clean this level first. )
#0| All right, I'll do it.</talk>
	</item>
	
	<item ID="402">
		<talk>#1| I don't quite understand.
#1| Why are you so obsessed with saving me?
#1| I'm not worth it.
#0| I have my reasons.
#0| And you deserve it.
#0| Besides, rabbit ghosts are too cool, I’m not okay with that.
#1| Ha ha ha, Fine! Guess I'll live a little longer, purrr!</talk>
	</item>
	
	<item ID="403">
		<talk>#1| We did it!
#0| That was not easy.
#1| I almost became a rabbit ghost, purrr.
#0| Not really, only spirits that regret very much when they die become ghosts.
#1| Regret?
#0| Yeah, I've been through that too before.
#1| So you really regret about losing your life after you die?
#0| Well, that's right...
#1|... So the reason you came to save me is because you regretted your lost life?
#0| Well, not just that...
#1| What else then?
#0| Because...
#1| ...I' m really disappointed.
#1| I'm leaving, and I won' t let you stop me this time. Goodbye.
#0| Wait!</talk>
	</item>
	
	<item ID="501">
		<talk>#1| You still can’t leave me alone.
#1| Why?
#2| I can't just let you die.-5001+I don't want you to die.-5002</talk>
	</item>
	
<item ID="502">
		<talk>#1| As I said, my life has no purpose or meaning.
#2| Life is meaningless.  -5003+  We can find it together. Calm down.-5004</talk>
	</item>
	
	<item ID="503">
		<talk>#2| Wait!-5005+You can't do this!-5006</talk>
	</item>
	
</root>